uplink.org 2017-12-14

# Builders Depot® Privacy Policy

Builders Depot is committed to respecting the privacy of our customers and all visitors to the Builders Depot web site. We do not make any attempt to identify visitors by name or e-mail address. If you make a purchase at our site we request only enough personal information for us to process and deliver your order. Here is how we handle the personal information that you provide us:

## **Why we need your information:**

  * **E-Mail address:**

> When you place an order, or contact us for any reason at the Builders Depot web site, you provide an e-mail address. The primary reason for this is so that our customer service department can respond to your inquiry or contact you with any questions they might have about your order. We will, from time to time, contact you via e-mail to let you know about new and interesting merchandise as well as special discount offers available at the Builders Depot web site. If you would rather we not contact you with this information via e-mail, please send us an e-mail to info@buildersdepot.com. Please mail the request from the e-mail address you wish to be excluded from such mailings.

  * **Telephone Number:**

> We ask for your phone number when you place an order at our web site. We will only call you if we need information to fill your order. We will not make a sales call to you, nor will we rent, sell or contribute your phone number to any third party or telemarketing operation.

  * **Credit Card Number:**

> We will not disclose any Builders Depot customer's credit card information to any third party, other than our clearinghouse and your bank (to charge the card). When your order is processed, your credit card information is deleted from our internet site.

  * **Name and Street Address:**

> When you place an order at the Builders Depot web site, your name and street address are entered into Builders Depot customer file. Builders Depot will use this address to send you updated catalogs and flyers via direct (U.S.) mail. Builders Depot will not rent, sell or otherwise distribute your name and address to any third party without your express permission.
> 
> In order to serve our customers better or to comply with evolving rules and practices governing consumer privacy on the internet, we may make changes to our privacy policy. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page. If you have any questions about Builders Depot's privacy policy, please send us an e-mail to [service@buildersdepot.com](http://buildersdepot.com/service@buildersdepot.com)

This privacy policy sets out how Builders Depot® uses and protects any information that you give Builders Depot® when you use this website. Builders Depot® is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Builders Depot® may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@buildersdepot.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 10-05 35th Ave Long Island City, NY 11106.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
